FRANCO COSTAMAGNA

PSYCHOLOGIST & FULL STACK DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- 351 3054365
- franco_costamagna@hotmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/franco-nicolas-costamagna/
- https://github.com/Francosta magna
- Cordoba, Argentina

TECHNOLOGIES

HTML

CSS

JAVASCRIPT

REACT.JS

NODE.JS

REDUX

EXPRESS

POSTRGESQL

SEOUELIZE

MINDAR

SKILLS

EMPATHY

CLIENT ORIENTED

PROACTIVE

PROBLEM SOLVING

TFAMWORK

COMUNICATION

FLEXIBILITY

SOCIABILITY

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Native English - C2

Portuguese - Basic

French - Basic

ABOUT ME

Full Stack Developer with Web Designer training. Experience working with NodeJS, React, Redux, SQL amongst other technologies.

I am also a Clinical Psychologist, profession that I carry out in the present, it has allowed me to develop comunicational soft skills, active listening and a better understanding of interrelationships inside groups.

My main goal over the last years has been to find ways to improve people's lives and mental health through technology.

I think myself as a proactive person, having developed several ventures since early age, being the most important one, an E-commerce dedicated to sell event accesories, wich is still active and in continous growth.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

E-COMMERCE - OWNER

2009 - Present | Zoa Accesorios

- Social Media publications design.
- Photography for posts.
- Importing products.
- FaceApp Development.

CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGIST

2017 - Present | Own Office

- Face to face and virtual sessions.
- Spanish and English speaking patients.
- · Couples and Group theraphy

EDUCATION

2010 - 2017

Psychology Degree.
Universidad Nacional de Córdoba

2022

Full Stack Web Developer. 700 hs of Theoretical-Practical training. Henry Bootcamp

PROYECTS

Full Stack Web Developer - Countries App sep. 22 - oct. 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Design and Development of a Countries App wich included: search, filters, ordering and creation of tourism activities.
- Front-end: React, Redux, CSS. Back-End: Node.js, Express. Database: PostgreSQL & Sequelize.

Deploy

Full Stack Web Developer - **TuPcIdeal** oct. 22 - nov. 22 Henry Bootcamp, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- I was part of a team who designed and developed a Market App of PC components, wich included: search, filters, ordering, product creation, shopping cart, favourites, and buyer-seller-admin-superadmin boards.
- Payment gateway with Mercadopago, E-mail notifications, etc.
- Front-End: React, Redux Toolkit, CSS. Back-End: Node.js, Express. Database: PostgreSQL, Sequelize. Firebase, Mercadopago SDK, and other technologies were used as well.

Deploy

Augmented Reality (MindAR) - FaceApp nov. 22 - present Zoa Accesorios, E-commerce, Córdoba, Argentina.

- I am currently developing a FaceApp to generate proximity between the product and the buyer. In this App, the potential buyers can try the product (head accesories) before buying it.
- This FaceApp is being developed in HTML and Javacript, using the MindAr augmented reality library. Three.js training was needed.

Repository

COURSES

2015

Psychological First Aid Universitat Autonoma de Barcelona

2015-2016

Postgrated in Rorschach Psychodiagnosis Centro Privado de Psicodiagnóstico

2016

Psychometric techniques for the work area Fundación Propade

2021

SQL basics Udemy

2022

Introduction to Web Ar development Udemy